{
    "home": {
        "noStreakTitle": "Welcome to Duotech! Select a course to proceed",
        "streakTitle": "Keep learning!"
    },
    "learn": {
        "topicHeader": {
            "title": "Unit 1",
            "description": "Discussing pertinent topics"
        },
        "topic": {
            "title": "All you need to know",
            "description": "Lesson 1 of 1",
            "start": "Start +100 coffees"
        }
    },
    "navbar": {
        "routes": ["learn"]
    },
    "widgets": {
        "coffees": {
            "title": "Coffees",
            "description": ["You have", "coffee(s)."]
        },
        "streak": {
            "title": "Streak",
            "description": ["streak day(s)"]
        },
        "lives": {
            "title": "Hearts",
            "description": ["Refill Hearts"]
        }
    },
    "lesson": {
        "title": "Answer the following question",
        "correct": "Let's correct the mistakes!",
        "button": {
            "check": "Check",
            "continue": "Continue"
        },
        "feedback": {
            "correct": ["Correct!", "That's it!", "Awesome!", "Fantastic!", "Great job!", "Bravo!"],
            "wrong": "Correct Solution:"
        },
        "finish": {
            "title": "Congratulations!",
            "coffees": "Coffees Gained",
            "streak": "Streak",
            "github": "See more projects"
        },
        "refill": {
            "title": "You ran out of hearts!",
            "main_description": "Use your coffees to buy hearts.",
            "secondary_description": "Insufficient coffees? No worries! Here's a little boost to fuel your lesson this time. Enjoy!",
            "coffees": "coffees",
            "lives": "hearts",
            "button": {
                "continue": "Continue",
                "refill": "Refill",
                "cancel": "End session"
            }
        },
        "bar": {
            "title": "Wait, don't go!",
            "description": "You're right on track! If you quit now, you'll lose your progress.",
            "keep": "Keep Learning",
            "end": "End Session"
        },
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Best way to declare variables?",
                "answers": ["let", "const", "var", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "Best media query breakpoint strategy?",
                "answers": ["mobile-first", "desktop-first", "it depends", "fluid"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Best framework for frontend?",
                "answers": ["React", "Vue", "Angular", "it depends", "Svelte", "HTMX"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "Best framework for backend?",
                "answers": ["Django", "Laravel", "Spring", "Express", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "Best database?",
                "answers": ["MongoDB", "it depends", "MySQL", "PostgreSQL"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "Best authentication method?",
                "answers": ["OAuth", "JWT", "it depends", "API key"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "Best build tool?",
                "answers": ["Webpack", "Parcel", "Rollup", "Gulp", "Browserify", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "What is the best development methodology?",
                "answers": ["waterfall", "scrum", "extreme programming", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "Best cloud platform?",
                "answers": ["AWS", "GCP", "Azure", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "Best documentation format?",
                "answers": ["Markdown", "HTML", "Docx", "it depends"],
                "solution": ["it depends"]
            }
        ]
    }
}